1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
41. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
45. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
53. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
61. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
65. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
69. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
73. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)